Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
- Box: 31, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: The British Health Service, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 26)
    Author: Julius Manson
  - Item 4: 100 Questions and Answers on the British National Health Service, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 26)
    Author: American Medical Association
  - Item 5: Report of Investigation into the Operation of the British Health Insurance Act, 1920; Publication (Box 31, Folder 26)
    Author: William T. Ramsey & Ordway Tead
  - Item 6: The National Health Service of Great Britain, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 26)
    Author: Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation
  - Item 7: A Plan of Health Insurance for British Columbia, 1935; Publication (Box 31, Folder 26)
    Author: British Columbia Department of the Provincial Secretary
  - Item 8: British Medical Education and the National Health Service, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 26)
    Notes: August 26, 1950
  - Item 9: British National Health Service, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 26)
    Author: R.K. McNickle
    Notes: January 12, 1949
- Box: 31, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Health Security for the Nation, 1938; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: John A. Kingsbury
    Notes: October 15, 1938
  - Item 2: Estimate of Expenditures for a National Health Insurance Program, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Health Insurance Interim Report, 1946; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Education and Labor
    Notes: July 1946
  - Item 4: The Costs of Health Insurance, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: George Soule
  - Item 5: The National Health Program Scheme, 1946; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: Earl E. Muntz
  - Item 6: How's Your Health?, 1947; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: Robert Friedman
  - Item 7: What Should Congress Do About Health Insurance, 1947; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: Ransdell Inc.
    Notes: June 3, 1947
  - Item 8: The Extent of the Health Coverage of Insurance Companies, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Notes: July-August 1949
  - Item 9: Public Health Insurance in the United States, 1947; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: Edward A. Marciniak
  - Item 10: Thoughts on Compulsory Health Insurance, Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: Insurance Economics Society of America
  - Item 11: What Will Compulsory Health Insurance Cost?, Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: Adolph Schmidt
  - Item 12: Washington, D.C., 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: Committee for the Nation's Health
  - Item 13: What Compulsory Medical Care Would Cost Eventually, 1946; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Item 14: What Health Insurance Would Mean to You, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: Oscar R. Ewing
    Notes: November 14, 1949
  - Item 15: Thoughts on Compulsory Health Insurance, Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Item 16: What is National Health Insurance, Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Item 17: What Are We Arguing About?, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: American Dental Association
  - Item 18: Health Insurance and the Public Health, 1935; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: Edgar Sydenstricker
  - Item 19: The Nation's Health and the American Pharmacist, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: John L. Thurston
    Notes: April 28, 1949
  - Item 20: Voluntary Insurance Against Sickness: Estimates for 1948, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Notes: January-February 1950
  - Item 21: The President's Health Proposals -- A Program for Action, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Notes: September 20, 1949
  - Item 22: The Truman National Health Program, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: J. Donald Kingsley
    Notes: April 23, 1949
  - Item 23: A Summary and Critical Analysis of the Medical-Features of the Wagner-Murray-Dingell Bill, 1943; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: Committee of Physicians
    Notes: December 30, 1943
  - Item 24: Hospitals and Health Insurance, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Notes: May 3, 1949
  - Item 25: Cost Estimates for National Health Insurance, 1949; Publication (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Author: I.S. Falk
- Box: 31, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Health Insurance for People 65 or Older, 1968; Publication (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Administrative Expenses of Retired Employees Health Benefits Act, 1965; Publication (Box 31, Folder 28)
    Notes: June 9, 1965
  - Item 3: A Profile of Group Health Insurance in Force in the United States, 1966; Publication (Box 31, Folder 28)
    Author: Health Insurance Association of America
    Notes: December 31, 1966
- Box: 31, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Dental Coverages, Publication (Box 31, Folder 29)
    Author: Lee R. Farmer
  - Item 2: The Colorado College Studies, 1962; Publication (Box 31, Folder 29)
    Author: Bentley B. Gilbert & Carl L. Roberts
    Notes: Spring 1962
  - Item 3: Coming Home: The Problem of After-Care, 1965; Publication (Box 31, Folder 29)
    Author: Robert N. Wilson
- Box: 31, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Fundamentals of the Federal Old-Age, Survivors, and Disability Insurance System, and the Medicare Program, 1966; Publication (Box 31, Folder 30)
    Author: David A. Ivry, Laurence J. Ackerman, Walter C. McKain
  - Item 2: Evaluation of Proposed Premium Rates, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Evaluation of Premium Rates for Government-Wide Uniform Health Benefit Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Elements of Health Insurance Today, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 30)
    Author: Odin W. Anderson
  - Item 5: Federal Employees Health Benefits Program, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 30)
    Notes: December 3, 1960
  - Item 6: Medical Care and Welfare, Publication (Box 31, Folder 30)
    Author: Foundation on Employee Health
  - Item 7: Digest of Drug Prescription Programs, 1966; Publication (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Box: 31, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Group Health Insurance Policies, 1963; Publication (Box 31, Folder 31)
    Author: New York Health Insurance Institute
  - Item 2: Health and Social Security for the American People, 1961; Publication (Box 31, Folder 31)
    Author: Wilbur J. Cohen
    Notes: January 10, 1961
  - Item 3: Health Insurance Programs in Industry, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 31)
    Notes: December 1954
  - Item 4: Health Insurance Coverage, 1971; Publication (Box 31, Folder 31)
    Notes: November 23, 1971
  - Item 5: Health Plan Grading System, 1969; Publication (Box 31, Folder 31)
    Author: University of California
  - Item 6: The Government-Wide Service Benefit Plan -- Blue Cross and Blue Shield for Federal Employees -- Needs Improved Administration, 1970; Publication (Box 31, Folder 31)
    Notes: October 20, 1970
  - Item 7: Health Insurance and Health Care Statistics, Publication (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Item 8: Health Insurance and Related Provisions of Public Law 89-97, 1965; Publication (Box 31, Folder 31)
- Box: 32, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Impact of Hospitalization Costs on Aged Beneficiaries, 1961; Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Notes: April 1961
  - Item 2: Improving the Effectiveness of Health Insurance and Prepayment, 1967; Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Author: Walter J. McNerny
    Notes: August 1, 1967
  - Item 3: Increase in Government's Contribution Under Federal Employees Health Benefits Program, 1973; Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Notes: July 10, 1973
- Box: 32, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Medicare: Benefits and Gaps, 1966; Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Author: Sidney Margolius
    Notes: June 1966
  - Item 2: Medicaid: The People's Health Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Author: Raymond S. Alexander, Simon Podair
- Box: 32, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Prepaid Dentistry, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Author: John H. Simons
  - Item 2: Questions and Answers on Health Insurance for the Aged, 1965; Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Private Health Insurance and Medical Care, 1968; Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: A Profile of the Health Insurance Public, 1959; Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Opportunities for Improving Administration of Government-Wide Indemnity Benefit Plan of Health Insurance for Federal Employees and Annuitants, 1972; Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Notes: May 22, 1972
- Box: 32, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Minnesota Studies in Vocational Rehabilitation, 1967; Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Author: Rene V. Dawis
  - Item 2: Postal Amendment to H.R. 12202, 1972; Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Notes: February 16, 1972
  - Item 3: The Hospital Insurance and Diagnostic Services Program in Canada, 1962; Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Author: Canada Department of National Health and Welfare
- Box: 32, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Selected List of Publications, 1961; Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Ways and Means
- Box: 32, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Medicaid: State Programs After Two Years, 1968; Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Author: Tax Foundation, Inc.
  - Item 2: Helping More People Meet Health Care Expenses, 1961; Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Author: Health Insurance Council
    Notes: December 31, 1961
- Box: 32, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Medicare, 1968; Publication (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Analysis of "Family Medical Care Under Three Types of Health Insurance", 1962; Publication (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: The Case for Socialized Medicine, 1961; Publication (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Author: R.W. Tucker
- Box: 32, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Health Insurance and Health Care Statistics, 1969; Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Box: 32, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Story of Jim Healy, 1951; Publication (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Author: Rupert Lockwood
    Notes: August 1951
- Box: 32, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: What High School Pupils Study, 1962; Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Box: 32, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Jobs for Which a High School Education is Preferred, but Not Essential, 1976; Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Box: 32, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Post Graduation Plans of Hawaii's 1961 High School Graduates, 1962; Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
    Author: Hawaii Joint Committee on Guidance and Employment of Youth
    Notes: July 1962
- Box: 32, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Enrollment Size and Educational Effectiveness of the High School, Publication (Box 32, Folder 13)
    Author: Grace Wright
- Box: 32, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Higher Education Amendments of 1966, Publication (Box 32, Folder 14)
    Notes: October 5, 1966
  - Item 2: Higher Education Amendments of 1966, Publication (Box 32, Folder 14)
    Notes: October 19, 1966
- Box: 32, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Hilo Harbor, HI, 1961; Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Public Works
    Notes: June 15, 1961
- Box: 32, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Maritime Hiring Halls, 1950; Publication (Box 32, Folder 16)
    Notes: June 12, 1950
- Box: 32, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Christmas and New Year's Plans in 232 Companies, 1963; Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Proc Prvni Maj, 1965; Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
    Author: Jiri Vancura
    Language: Czechoslovakian.
  - Item 3: Monday Holidays, 1968; Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
    Notes: April 4, 1968
  - Item 4: Dartnell Three-Year Calendar of Important Holidays, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Memorial Day and Fourth of July Time-Off Policies, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Paid Holidays in Major Contracts, 1962; Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
    Notes: June 22, 1962
  - Item 7: List of Important Holidays, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
    Author: The Dartnell Corporation
  - Item 8: Christmas and Year-End Personnel Practices, 1968; Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Box: 32, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Management Holidays, 1972; Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: The Staggering of Holidays, 1945; Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Labour and National Service
- Box: 32, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Holiday Policies, Publication (Box 32, Folder 19)
    Author: Commerce & Industry Association of New York
- Box: 32, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Results of Holiday Policy Questionnaire, 1948; Publication (Box 32, Folder 20)
    Author: New York Personnel Management Association
    Notes: December 15, 1948
- Box: 32, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Management Problems of Homemakers Employed Outside the Home, Publication (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Box: 32, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Industrial Homework, 1961; Publication (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Box: 32, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Heimarbeit, 1966; Publication (Box 32, Folder 23)
    Author: Westdeutscher Verlag
- Box: 32, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Industrial Homework Law, 1941; Publication (Box 32, Folder 24)
    Author: New Jersey Department of Labor
    Notes: July 28, 1941
  - Item 2: Industrial Home Work Law, 1941; Publication (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Industrial Home Work Law, Publication (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Box: 32, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Activities of New York Bureau of Homework Inspection, 1947; Publication (Box 32, Folder 25)
    Author: New York Bureau of Homework Inspection
    Notes: January 1947
- Box: 32, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Brief Summary of State Laws Regulating Industrial Homework, 1964; Publication (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Box: 32, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Labour Department and Trade Union Education, Publication (Box 32, Folder 27)
    Author: Hong Kong Labor Department
- Box: 32, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Survey of Government Wages and Salaries, 1963; Publication (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Box: 32, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: The Full-Fashioned Hosiery Industry in Pennsylvania, 1950; Publication (Box 32, Folder 29)
    Author: Pennsylvania Bureau of Employment and Unemployment Compensation
- Box: 32, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: The Full-Fashioned Hosiery Industry in Puerto Rico, 1947; Publication (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Box: 32, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Report of Task Force on Principles of Payment for Hospital Care, 1963; Publication (Box 32, Folder 31)
    Author: American Hospital Association
  - Item 2: Human Relations in the Hospital Industry, Publication (Box 32, Folder 31)
    Author: Thomas R. O'Donovan
- Box: 32, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Model Constitution and By-Laws for a Voluntary Hospital, 1948; Publication (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: Report of the Committee on Inclusive Rates, 1945; Publication (Box 32, Folder 32)
    Notes: May 12, 1945
  - Item 3: Organization Guide for Hospital Volunteer Service, 1944; Publication (Box 32, Folder 32)
    Notes: July 1944
  - Item 4: Reducing Costs in Hospitals, 1966; Publication (Box 32, Folder 32)
    Author: Center for the Study of Productivity Motivation
  - Item 5: The Market for Hospital Care, 1962; Publication (Box 32, Folder 32)
    Author: Robert L. Robertson
- Box: 32, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Highlights from Survey of Psychiatric Aides, 1964; Publication (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: First Institute on Hospital Personnel Management, 1944; Publication (Box 32, Folder 33)
    Notes: June 26-30, 1944
- Box: 32, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Earnings of Hospital Employees in New York State, 1969; Publication (Box 32, Folder 34)
    Author: New York State Department of Health
- Box: 32, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Reporting of Hospitalization, 1961; Publication (Box 32, Folder 35)
- Box: 32, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: The Development of Sound Personnel Practices in Hospitals, 1948; Publication (Box 32, Folder 36)
- Box: 32, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: A Program for Hospital Incentives, 1962; Publication (Box 32, Folder 37)
    Author: Donald C. Carner
  - Item 2: Hospitals Under the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1972; Publication (Box 32, Folder 37)
    Notes: February 1972
  - Item 3: Hospital Use by Diagnosis, 1961; Publication (Box 32, Folder 37)
    Author: Monroe Lerner
  - Item 4: Hospitals Under the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1973; Publication (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Item 5: Hospital Rate Survey, 1950; Publication (Box 32, Folder 37)
- Box: 32, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Wages and Hours in Hotels and Other Establishments, 1947; Publication (Box 32, Folder 38)
    Author: New York Department of Labor
- Box: 32, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Eating and Drinking Places Industry, 1969; Publication (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: Restaurants and Food Service Employees, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 39)
    Notes: October 1971
  - Item 3: The Rehabilitation of the Catering Industry, 1945; Publication (Box 32, Folder 39)
- Box: 32, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Hotel and Restaurant Job Opportunities, 1965; Publication (Box 32, Folder 40)
    Author: California Department of Employment
- Box: 32, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Manpower Requirements of the Hospitality Industry, 1967; Publication (Box 32, Folder 41)
    Author: Canadian Department of Manpower and Immigration
- Box: 32, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Your Manpower, 1967; Publication (Box 32, Folder 42)
    Author: Great Britain Economic Development Committee for Hotels and Catering
- Box: 32, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Hotels and Motels Under the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1973; Publication (Box 32, Folder 43)
    Notes: March 1973
- Box: 32, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: An Economic Report on Hotels, Restaurants, and Laundries in the Virgin Islands, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 44)
- Box: 32, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Preliminary Report on the Resort Industry in Sullivan County, 1964; Publication (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Item 2: Employment in the Sullivan County Resort Industry, 1968; Publication (Box 32, Folder 45)
- Box: 32, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Joint Report of Engineers on Transition to 40-Hour -- 5-Day Week to Board of Transportation of the City of New York, NY, 1951; Publication (Box 32, Folder 46)
    Author: Day & Zimmermann, Inc.
    Notes: May 23, 1951
  - Item 2: Law of Shops and Establishments, 1967; Publication (Box 32, Folder 46)
    Author: M. Shafi
  - Item 3: Eight Hours by Act of Congress, Publication (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Item 4: Report of Committee on Double Day-Shift Working, 1947; Publication (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Item 5: Studies of the Effects of Long Working Hours, 1944; Publication (Box 32, Folder 46)
    Author: Max D. Kossoris
    Notes: October 17, 1944
- Box: 32, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Die Gesetzlichen Feiertage und Ihre Entlohnung, 1967; Publication (Box 32, Folder 47)
    Author: Betriebs-Kurier
- Box: 32, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Lord's Day Observance, 1894; Publication (Box 32, Folder 48)
    Notes: May 2, 1894
- Box: 32, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Maximum Hour Legislation in France, 1941; Publication (Box 32, Folder 49)
    Notes: January 1941
- Box: 32, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Hours of Employment of Women and Young Persons Employed in Factories, 1969; Publication (Box 32, Folder 50)
    Author: Department of Employment and Productivity
  - Item 2: Health of Munition Workers Committee, 1917; Publication (Box 32, Folder 50)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Munitions
  - Item 3: Shorter Hours Longer Holidays, 1965; Publication (Box 32, Folder 50)
- Box: 33, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Effectuation of the Reduced Work Week, 1951; Publication (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Author: New York City Special Transit Committee
    Notes: December 26, 1951
  - Item 2: Transition to a 40-Hour Week, 1951; Publication (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 27, 1951
  - Item 3: Long Hours and Night Work: Experiences and Views of Women Workers, 1946; Publication (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Notes: May 1946
  - Item 4: Long Hours and Night Work: Experiences and Views of Women Workers, 1946; Publication (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Box: 33, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Innstilling om Forkortning av den Alminnelige Arbeidstid fra 45 til 42.5 Time Pr. Uke, 1966; Publication (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Author: Trykt I Engers Boktrykkeri
    Notes: December 15, 1966
    Language: Norwegian.
- Box: 33, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Rabochii Den'I Kommunizm, 1959; Publication (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Author: Strumilin, Stanislav Gustavovich
  - Item 2: Rabochii den'I Ego Ispol'zouanie, 1969; Publication (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Author: A. Ia. Andreenko
- Box: 33, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Business Review, 1968; Publication (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Author: Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas
- Box: 33, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A Quick Look at Hours Worked, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Economics of the Shorter Workweek, 1964; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: February 1964
  - Item 3: Interpretation of Emergency Calls as Hours Worked, 1956; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Author: NAM Law Department
    Notes: August 6, 1956
  - Item 4: Length of the Workweek, 1958; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Can We Win the Peace with a 40-Hour Week?, 1948; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Author: C.E. Wilson
    Notes: April 20, 1948
  - Item 6: Maximum Weekly Hours Set By State Labor Laws for Women, 1955; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: July 1, 1955
  - Item 7: Maximum Daily Hours Set By State Labor Laws for Women, 1955; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: How the Workweek is Decreasing, 1958; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: February 21, 1958
  - Item 9: Maximum Weekly Hours Set by State Labor Laws for Women, 1956; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: July 1, 1956
  - Item 10: The Thirty-Hour Week, 1935; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Author: Harold G. Moulton & Maurice Leven
    Notes: January 3, 1935
  - Item 11: Maximum Daily Hours Set by State Labor Laws for Women, 1956; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: The History of the Shorter Workday, 1942; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Author: Labor Research Association
  - Item 13: The Shorter Work Week, 1934; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: December 1934
  - Item 14: The Issue of the Shorter Workweek, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)